Guide to the Darinka Archive 1973-2010 MSS 340
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
Darinka Archive
1973-2010
MSS 340
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
10.0 boxes
Darinka: A Performance Studio was opened in 1984 by Gary Ray Bugarcic (aka Gary Ray). The club served as a venue for artists of all disciplines, including performance, theatre, music, dance, film, video, fine art, and poetry and prose, until its closing in 1987. The archive includes reviews, letters, subject files, contracts, flyers, stencils, photographs, audio and video recordings of performances, and digital data storage disks.
Bugarcic, Gary Ray
Biographical/Historical note
Darinka: A Performance Studio was opened on April 21, 1984 by Gary Ray Bugarcic (aka Gary Ray). The club served as a venue for artists of all disciplines, including performance, theatre, music, dance, film, video, fine art, and poetry and prose. In keeping with the Eastern European roots of the East Village/Lower East Side, the club was named after Gary’s mother, who was Croatian born. Darinka is a derivative of the Slavic word dar, meaning “gift.”
The club was located at 118 East First Street, two doors down from Avenue A, and had a speakeasy type entrance under the residential stoop of the building. Up to the late 1970s, the space was used as a local Italian Social Club until a fire destroyed it. During the renovation of the space, all the old charred beams were laid in the backyard to provide an urban rustic wood patio enjoyed by patrons during the hot summer months. The interior of the club had a small proscenium stage that was described by many as looking like a live television. A variety of local painters such as James Romberger and Mark Kostabi showed their work on the walls of the club until the permanent murals and stencils were painted. Regular performers included They Might Be Giants (considered the house band), performance artist Steve Buscemi (still a fireman when he started performing), Karen Finley, Jack Smith, Charles Long, William Pope L., Kembra Pfahler, Nick Zedd, Anna Deavere Smith, and John S. Hall. In addition, there were many writers who regularly read during the Sunday prose and poetry nights, including Darius James, Patrick McGrath, Hal Sirowitz, Lynne Tillman, Mark Dery, Nina Zivancevic, Peter Cherches, Bob Holman, Ira Cohen and Taylor Meade.
On June 29, 1985, the NYPD raided the club during a mushroom party and performance by artists David West and Andy Somma. Gary Ray and the bartender, Robin Clements, were arrested for operating an unlicensed bottle club. Several months later Darinka reopened as a private club with Randy Lee Hartwig and John Gernand as managers. As a private club each new member would fill out a membership application card upon entrance. The application cards were kept in a file near the door in case of police inquiry. Membership cards were also distributed.
Darinka was the first home of "The Church of the Little Green Man.” The church was founded by conceptual artist Mike Osterhout and had its first service in December of 1986. Darinka closed in May of 1987.
Articles mentioning Darinka have appeared in The Village Voice, New York magazine, Performance, East Village Eye, Toronto Globe and Mail, The New York Times, and The Drama Review (Spring 1985). The club is also acknowledged in the documentary Gigantic: A Tale Of Two Johns.
Gary Ray Bugarcic, a graduate of The American Academy of Dramatic Arts, has worked as an actor and stage director in almost every downtown New York theatrical venue. As a musician, he played in several bands, including State of Desire and The Academy, which performed regularly at CBGB and Danceteria before opening Darinka. After closing the club he toured with Karen Finley in her play The Theory of Total Blame and worked with The Ridge Theatre Company as well as with Kestutis Nakas and in Jeff Weiss’s “Hot Keys.” He has also appeared in such indie films as Todd Haynes’ Poison and Desperately Seeking Susan. New Blood magazine published his poetry in the 1980s and his “3-D Lenticular Photographs of the Eighties” have been shown in several New York City galleries, including the Participant Gallery.
Scope and Content
The Darinka Archive contains material kept by Gary Ray Bugarcic, founder of the Darinka Nightclub and performance space. It includes reviews, letters, subject files, contracts, flyers, stencils, photographs, audio and video recordings of performances, and digital data storage disks.
Arrangement
This collection is separated into six series:
Series I: Darinka Files
Series II: Playbills
Series III: Audio Recordings
Series IV: Video Recordings
Series V: Data Storage
Series I, III, IV, and V are arranged alphabetically. Series II is arranged chronologically.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
Bugarcic, Gary Ray; Alternative rock music.; Alternative spaces (Arts facilities); Audiocassettes.; Downtown writers.; East Village (New York, N.Y.); Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.); Performance art.; Photographs.; Printed ephemera.; Punk rock music.; Videocassettes.
- Series I: Darinka Files
  Scope and Content
  This series contains material created and kept by Darinka. It includes administrative and legal papers, ephemera such as flyers and ticket stubs, press, T-shirts, and photographs.
  - Address Book (1 of 4), c. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Address Book (2 of 4), c. 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Address Book (3 of 4), Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Address Book (3 of 4), Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Theatre Script, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Becky Letter", 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - C.V. / Resume / Chronology, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Church of the Little Green Man, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Clay Spohn, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Club Promo Material, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "Confessions of a Peyote Eater", Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Darinka Flyers: Music and Dance", c. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Darinka Flyers: Performance Etc., c. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Darinka Flyers: Prose / Poetry", 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Darinka Flyers - "Yellow Folder", c. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Darinka Stencils, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Early Darinka Flyers", c. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Film Series posters, c. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Flyers - original, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Headshots, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Huntin'" / "Bodybag", c. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Letters, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Letters and contracts, 1981-1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "Misc. Letters", 1981-1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Misc. Posters, Scripts, Announcements, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Misc. Programs, flyers, postcards, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Misc. Programs, flyers, programs, 1980-2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "Nepotism", 1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - New York City leases, 1990, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - New York City subway map, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - New York Magazine, June 17, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - "Non-Darinka flyers" (CBGB's, etc...), Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - "Organic Extensionism", 1995 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Postcards (1 of 2), 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Postcards (2 of 2), 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - "Press", c. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Promo cards, c. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Pull the Lever / PS 122, c. 1994 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - "Reviews / Press", 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - "Ridiculous Theatrical Co. etc.", 1985-2003 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - "S. Past - Ireg.", Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Tickets / Stubs / Button, 1980-1993 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - "Tourist Season" shoot, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Typhoid Mary 911 script, Undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - T-Shirt - "The Love Club", Undated (Box 6, Object ID: 340.2.0001)
  - T-Shirt - "Ridiculous Theatrical Co. presents Oscar Wilde's Salome", Undated (Box 6, Object ID: 340.2.0002)
  - T-Shirt - "Ridiculous Theatrical Co. presents Turds in Hell", Undated (Box 6, Object ID: 340.2.0003)
  - T-Shirt - "Viva Carlo! Viva Livertad!" David Wojnarowicz illustration, Undated (Box 6, Object ID: 340.2.0004)
  - "This Performance Sold Out" sign, Undated (Object ID: 340.2.0005)
- Series II: Playbills
  This series contains collected playbills, including several from the Ridiculous Theatrical Company.
  - Playbills (1 of 5), 1970-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Playbills (2 of 5), 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Playbills (3 of 5), 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Playbills (4 of 5), 1996-2010 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Playbills (5 of 5), 1996-2010 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Series III: Audio Recordings
  This series contains all audio recordings stored on magnetic audiocassettes. It includes live performances at Darinka, compilation tapes, demo tapes, and miscellaneous recordings organized alphabetically by artist or project title. Access copies may not be available, please ask a Fales archivist.
  - Subseries A: Performance
    This subseries contains audio recordings of performances at Darinka and other venues.
    - [A: The Academy, "Windows Closed" "Sidewalk" "Work Tape" "1st Time"]; [B: Jaco Pastorius "Live!" "w/Great Harp Player"], July 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0001)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Format: Audiocassette
    - "Academy I copyright tape 10-1-83", October 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0002)
    - The Academy - CBGB's 10-20-83., October 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0003)
    - [A: Academy 12-3-83 CBGB's]; [B:12-3-83 cont, 10-20-83], 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0004)
    - 10-9-83 Fives; The Academy, October 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0005)
    - "Academy w/EYAL 12-83", December 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0006)
    - The Academy 12-3-83 CBGB's., December 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0007)
    - Academy 12-28-83 CBGB's, December 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0008)
    - The Academy - Cosmic Pig Roast, December 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0009)
    - The Academy. 4-Track recorded at Dubway Studio., Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0010)
    - The Academy - 4-Track recorded at Dubway Studio., 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0011)
    - The Academy. 10/20/83.CBGB's., October 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0012)
    - The Academy live., 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0013)
    - The Academy copyright 1983. (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0014)
    - The Academy 3-10-83 CBGB's., March 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0015)
    - Academy 3-10-84 CBGB's., March 1984 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0016)
    - Academy. CBGB's. 4-6-84., April 1984 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0017)
    - "Academy. 1st Rehearse 7/84.", July 1984 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0018)
    - Academy of Nuns. CBGB's. Pressure Point, Down the Line. Jam 8/84., August 1984 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0019)
    - Academy 12-7-84 CB's., December 1984 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0020)
    - "Academy of Nuns (Master)", Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0021)
    - The Academy: 2 Songs., 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0022)
    - "Statue w/Dave Gerad." Academy 12/4., December 1984 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0023)
    - Academy - "Woodstone Project", Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0024)
    - The Academy, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0025)
    - [A: Academy]; [B: Rehearsal; Piano Music; Academy Rehearsal; Bill + Steve], Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0026)
    - Academy. Al - Steve Logan. Bill - Norm., Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0027)
    - The Academy, "Lonesome Runner", Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0028)
    - The Academy - 2 Songs., Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0029)
    - The Academy Demo tape, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0030)
    - The Academy: 2 Songs, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0031)
    - 4 Track - Broken Glass Live, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0032)
    - "Chump Change w/Bad Vocals", Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0033)
    - "Cowboy Work Tape", Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0034)
    - "TUBOB I", Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0035)
    - Big Bang Live at the Batcave, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0036)
    - Church of the Little Green Man, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0037)
    - Church of the Little Green Man Radio, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0038)
    - Epileptic Fitness "I-II", Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0039)
    - Epileptic Fitness "III - IV", Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0040)
    - Edward L. Gordon "Colage", 1978 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0041)
    - Karen Finley Interview, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0042)
    - Jickets, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0043)
    - Hugo Largo at Darinka, 1985 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0044)
    - Hayes Lazar/Vocals, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0045)
    - Haze Laser "Rock of My Heart", Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0046)
    - Over-Knife Sensation Luxury Knives 4/18/1982, April 1982 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0047)
    - Ambient Laragi, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0048)
    - Luxury Knives CBGB's 1/14/83, January 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0049)
    - Fall 82 Knives w/Peter Earth, 1982 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0050)
    - New Year's Eve 12/31/82 Luxury Knives, December 1982 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0051)
    - Gary & Jeff Demo, February 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0052)
    - Luxury Knives Rehearsal 2/13/1982, February 1982 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0053)
    - Luxury Knives 3/13/1983, March 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0054)
    - Luxury Knives, May 1983 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0055)
    - Early Work Tape Luxury Knives, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0056)
    - Luxury Knives, "Buried Alive" etc., Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0057)
    - Luxury Knives G.T., Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0058)
    - Luxury Knives - Sunday Knives, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0059)
    - Luxury Knives, 5 Song Demo Tapes, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0060)
    - Luxury Knives - Psycho Jamboree, Undated (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0061)
    - Purple Geezus, "Jennifer Polanski", 1988 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0062)
    - Purple Geezus, "V.S.O.P.", 1987 (Box 7, Cassette ID: 340.0063)
    - Sonorexia, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0064)
    - State of Desire, 1/82 CBGB's, January 1982 (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0065)
    - State of Desire CBGB's 6/12/1982, June 1982 (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0066)
    - State of Desire Rehearsal New Tunes, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0067)
    - State of Desire, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0068)
    - State of Desire Rehearsal, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0069)
    - State of Desire w/Messages, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0070)
    - Trumbull High School, May 1974 (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0071)
    - Sum 1 Ron Schlossberg JAM, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0072)
    - Sum 1 w/Haze, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0073)
    - Sum 1, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0074)
    - They Might Be Giants, 1985 (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0075)
    - They Might Be Giants, 1985 (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0076)
    - They Might Be Giants Intro, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0077)
    - They Might Be Giants, "They Got Lost", Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0078)
    - Walter Thompson - WKCR, December 1984 (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0079)
    - "Toyko Tower" [sp], Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0080)
    - Tokyo Tower - Bass Line, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0081)
    - Tokyo Tower - Phone Messages, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0082)
    - "Tokyko Tower" [sp] 3/6/1989 (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0083)
    - Tokyo Tower, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0084)
    - Circus Assault - Master, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0085)
    - Circus Assault - Show tape, September 1986 (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0086)
    - Disco House - Subliminal, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0087)
    - Bass, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0088)
    - Kung Fu Fighting, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0089)
    - Take 1, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0090)
    - B + B + Me, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0091)
    - Patrick, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0092)
    - Decca-Dance, 1983 (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0093)
    - Curtis Gone Bad, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0094)
    - Jeff Music Ideas, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0095)
    - 3 Song Demo Jeff Ideas, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0096)
    - Jeff 5/28, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0097)
    - Peter, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0098)
    - Avant-Garde, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0099)
  - Subseries B: Darinka Music
    This subseries contains compilation tapes of music played at Darinka.
    - Art of Noise, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0100)
    - Assorted Party music, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0101)
    - Sonny Averona, "Live At Palumbo's", Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0102)
    - Adrian Belew, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0103)
    - B-Funk, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0104)
    - Pay Back, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0105)
    - Cab, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0106)
    - Club Funk, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0107)
    - Club Tape, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0108)
    - Gato Barbieri, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0109)
    - Elvis Costello, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0110)
    - Sam Cooke, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0111)
    - Dance I, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0112)
    - Dance Tape II, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0113)
    - Jazz Dance III, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0114)
    - Dance IV, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0115)
    - Dance IV, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0116)
    - Dance Up and Down, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0117)
    - Dark and Arabian Feel, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0118)
    - Miles Davis - Terry Gibbs, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0119)
    - Diva, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0120)
    - Diva Original Soundtrack, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0121)
    - DJ Mix: New Order, Cocteau Twins, Soul Sonic, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0122)
    - Eurythmics, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0123)
    - Fun Boy 3, "Colour Field", Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0124)
    - Fun Boy 3, "Waiting", Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0125)
    - D. Bowie, "Pinups", Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0126)
    - Gay Tunes For Gary, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0127)
    - Tom Waits, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0128)
    - Joe Jackson, OMD…, Undated (Box 8, Cassette ID: 340.0129)
    - George Jones, "The Race Is On", Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0130)
    - King Pleasure, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0131)
    - Fela Kuti, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0132)
    - On the Run I Waited, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0133)
    - London Radio, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0134)
    - Lounge Lizards/Blue Hawaii, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0135)
    - Motown Gold, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0136)
    - Mr. Lee, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0137)
    - Murray the K Show - 1963, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0138)
    - New Order, Promenaders, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0139)
    - New Sounds, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0140)
    - OMD - PIL, Wall of Voodoo, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0141)
    - Party Mix, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0142)
    - SALSA, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0143)
    - Police, Patsy Cline, Crazy, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0144)
    - Elvis Presley, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0145)
    - Throbbing Gristle, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0146)
    - The Rage of 1710's, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0147)
    - Roxy Music, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0148)
    - Roxy Music, "Flesh and Blood," Bowie, "Ashes to Ashes", Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0149)
    - Sakamoto; James Brown, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0150)
    - Satie: Parade, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0151)
    - Thomas Schippers Conducts Samuel Barber, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0152)
    - Simple Minds, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0153)
    - Ska, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0154)
    - Stargazers, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0155)
    - TOTB - Theory of Total Blame - Las Vegas, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0156)
    - Tears, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0157)
    - Debussy: Prelude al'apres-midi d'un faune, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0158)
    - U.N.C.L.E. - Soundtrack, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0159)
    - Via Afrika, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0160)
    - Village Music of Bulgaria, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0161)
    - Steve Winwood, "Chronicles", Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0162)
    - Yellow Magic Orchestra, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0163)
    - Yello - Elvis - Devo, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0164)
    - Yello and Devo, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0165)
  - Subseries C: Demos and Miscellaneous
    This subseries contains various demo tapes and unidentified material.
    - The Actuals, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0166)
    - Alien Planetscapes, "Skylore", Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0167)
    - Green Night Audio Leter, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0168)
    - Jole Blonde, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0169)
    - Jenny Bruce, "Demo Tape", Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0170)
    - Bump, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0171)
    - Doomster, "Refreshes While You Smoke", Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0172)
    - Howard #1, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0173)
    - Loser's Preshow Song, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0174)
    - Loser's Preshow Music (Matter of Time), Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0175)
    - Nirvana, "Nevermind", Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0176)
    - Martland Peters 1 & 2, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0177)
    - David Algeo Smith, "Demo", Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0178)
    - Stephan Smith, "The Ballad of Abner Louima", Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0179)
    - Jeff & Gary 3 Song Demo, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0180)
    - Tellus: The Audio Cassette Magazine #10, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0181)
    - Tellus: The Audio Cassette Magazine #20, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0182)
    - Unfinished Journey, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0183)
    - Wedding Ceremony, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0184)
    - Luxury Knives Demo Tape, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0185)
    - Luxury Knives Demo Tape, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0186)
    - Luxury Knives Demo Tape, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0187)
    - Early Recording, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0188)
    - Don't Do Me Any Favors Pre-Show & House, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0189)
    - [Unknown], Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0190)
    - [Unknown], Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0191)
    - [Unknown], Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0192)
    - [Unknown], Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0193)
    - [Jousd #5], Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0194)
    - [Other Side Jam w/Rob - Guitar; Chuck - Drum], Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0195)
    - [Unknown], Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0196)
    - Gemini cassette head cleaner, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0197)
    - Audio cassette head cleaner, Undated (Box 9, Cassette ID: 340.0198)
  - Subseries D: Additional Sound Recordings
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
    Audiovisual materials in Subseries D are commmercially released material and are available to researchers.
    - After the Fall #12, Undated (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
      Format: Sound Disc: Digital; 4 3/4 in.
    - Below Houston #4, Undated (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
    - Black and White World #1, Undated (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
    - Black and White World #3, Undated (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
    - RobK ExCorpse, Undated (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)
    - Workdogs In Hell, 1992 (Box 11, Disk ID: N/A)